

CONTACT

+54 9 1134908167

tebeckford@gmail.com

https://tebeck.vercel.app

Buenos Aires, Argentina

EDUCATION

2015 - 2018 - ISIV Senior Systems Analyst

2017 - DIGITAL HOUSE Full Stack Web Developer

EXPERTISE SKILLS

React Advanced (5+ years)

Typescript Intermediate (3+ years)

NextJS Advanced (4+ years)

SASS Advanced (4+ years)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Spanish Native

English Upper-intermediate B2

THOMAS E.BECKFORD

FRONTEND ENGINEER

ABOUT ME

As an experienced developer with a proven track record in the software industry, I specialize in designing and building complex systems using Typescript, React, and Node. I have a strong commitment to learning and growing in my career, as well as the ability to work effectively as part of a team. I am highly versatile and productive, with a talent for quickly adapting to new technologies and working efficiently under pressure.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Feb 2019 - 2023 - SOYMENU

As a Software Developer, I created, design and push to prod an application where restaurants can easily create their own user and set up their restaurantes to have a QR menu for their clients.

Skills: NextJS, SASS, React, TS, API Rest

Founder

Aug 2022 - 2023 - FUEL

As a frontend developer working in FUEL, I have gained valuable knowledge in creating modern solutions that cater to the needs of both creators and users. Skills: EthersJS \cdot Web3 \cdot Next.js \cdot Vercel \cdot Turborepo \cdot React query \cdot Axios \cdot Mantine.dev \cdot Chakra ui \cdot React.js

Senior Frontend Developer

Jun 2021 - Aug 2022 - SPIRITSWAP

Designed and developed a cutting-edge financial application from scratch, utilizing advanced programming languages and technologies to achieve high performance and user satisfaction. Check it out at https://spiritswap.finance Skills: EthersJS · Web3 · Chakra ui · React · Redux.js

Frontend Developer

Oct 2018 - Jun 2021 - KUBIKWARE

Full stack web developer at Kubikware, successfully initiating and completing multiple React and Nextjs projects from scratch. Expertise in creating efficient and user-friendly websites using Atomic Design system. Skilled in developing high-quality web applications that meet client needs. Skills: REST · Amazon Web Services (AWS) · PostgreSQL · Express.js · Next.js · Node · React · Redux.js Full Stack Developer